A Finding Aid to the Henri Gallery Records, circa early 1900s, 1940-1996, bulk 1957-1995, in the Archives of American Art AAA.henrgall
Archives of American Art
- Alphabetical Files, 1947-1996; Series 2; 50.1 Linear feet Boxes 3-52, 55-57, OV 58
  - Name Files, 1947-1996; 2.1
    - Doyle, Tom, 1972 (Box 16, Folder 24)
    - Drasites, Roy R., 1975 (Box 16, Folder 25)
    - Dreyer, Clarice, circa 1980-1986 (Box 16, Folder 26)
    - Drisch, Russell, 1974-1980 (Box 16, Folder 27)
    - Drucker, Elizabeth, 1986 (Box 16, Folder 28)
    - Du Bois, Guy Pène, 1972-1974 (Box 16, Folder 29)
    - Duchamp, Marcel, 1964-1991 (Box 16, Folder 30)
    - Duerst, Elvin, 1967 (Box 16, Folder 31)
    - Dufferer, William S., 1967-1969 (Box 16, Folder 32)
    - East Carolina University, 1995 (Box 16, Folder 33)
    - Edelson, Mary Beth, 1968-1993 (Box 16, Folder 34-35)
    - Edelson, Mary Beth, 1993; 1968-circa 1979 (Box 17, Folder 1-7)
    - Edelson, Mary Beth, "The Group", circa 1970s-1980s (Box 17, Folder 8)
    - Edwards, Tom, 1975 (Box 17, Folder 9)
    - Eldred, Dale, 1965-1969 (Box 17, Folder 10)
    - Elkins, Al, 1977 (Box 17, Folder 11)
    - Elliott, Anne Leyden, 1977-1978 (Box 17, Folder 12)
    - Elliott, Dennis, 1977-1982 (Box 17, Folder 13)
    - Elliott, Stanley B., 1968-1970 (Box 17, Folder 14)
    - Ellsworth, Robert, 1989-1992 (Box 17, Folder 15)
    - Engelson, Carol, 1974 (Box 17, Folder 16)
    - English, Marc, 1992 (Box 17, Folder 17)
    - Esposito, Diego, 1971-1972 (Box 17, Folder 18)
    - Estaban, Juan, undated (Box 17, Folder 19)
    - Evelyn, Leya, 1985, undated (Box 17, Folder 20)
    - Exton, Leslie, 1976-1995 (Box 17, Folder 21-26)
    - Eyans, Helen, undated (Box 17, Folder 27)
    - Fadeley, Kenneth, 1976-1979 (Box 17, Folder 28)
    - Fahlen, Charles, 1973-1974 (Box 18, Folder 1)
    - Falzoni, Giordano, 1964 (Box 18, Folder 2)
    - Farris, Linda (Gallery East, Seattle, WA), 1972 (Box 18, Folder 3)
    - Faudi, Freddie, 1970-1972; 1980-1981 (Box 18, Folder 4)
    - Faulkner, Frank, 1977-1992 (Box 18, Folder 5)
    - Feldman, Joel, 1978; 1973 (Box 18, Folder 6)
    - Fellows, Alice, 1973 (Box 18, Folder 7)
    - Ferguson, John, 1990-1994; 1971-1981 (Box 18, Folder 8-11)
      Oversized material housed in OV 58
    - Ferguson, Kathleen, 1978-1980; 1972 (Box 18, Folder 12)
    - Ferguson, Mary Carfagno, 1993-1995; 1981 (Box 18, Folder 13)
    - Ferrer, Rafael, 1989; 1970-1977 (Box 18, Folder 14)
    - Ferri, Steven, 1993-1994 (Box 18, Folder 15)
    - Fields, Ted, 1967 (Box 18, Folder 16)
    - Figueroa, Raimundo, 1983-1987 (Box 18, Folder 17)
    - Fine Arts Museum of the South, 1990-1994 (Box 18, Folder 18)
    - Fink, Stuart J., 1983-1986; 1991 (Box 18, Folder 19)
    - Finn, David, 1974-1990 (Box 18, Folder 20)
    - Firestone, Merton, 1991-1992 (Box 18, Folder 21)
    - Fisher, Suzanne L., 1989-1995 (Box 18, Folder 22-23)
    - Fisher, Vernon, 1971-1978 (Box 18, Folder 24-25)
    - Fishman, Louise, 1993 (Box 18, Folder 26)
    - Fleicher, Rachel, 1979-1984 (Box 18, Folder 27)
    - Foolery, Tom, 1980-1984 (Box 18, Folder 28)
    - Foppiano, Gustavo, 1959 (Box 19, Folder 1)
    - Ford, John, 1987 (Box 19, Folder 2)
    - Forgey, Ben, 1992-1994 (Box 19, Folder 3)
    - Forte, Mary, 1983-1986 (Box 19, Folder 4)
    - Foster, Francis, before 1981 (Box 19, Folder 5)
    - Fowler, Bob, 1974 (Box 19, Folder 6)
    - Frames by Rebecca, Inc., 1994-1995 (Box 19, Folder 7)
    - Frazier, Charles, 1971-1976 (Box 19, Folder 8-9)
    - Fredman, Faiya R., circa 1979 (Box 19, Folder 10)
    - Freed, Kenneth, 1980-1983 (Box 19, Folder 11)
    - Freedman, Ben, 1983-1990 (Box 19, Folder 12)
    - Freedman, Jacqueline, 1982-1995 (Box 19, Folder 13-15)
    - Freeland, Bill, circa 1973; 1989 (Box 19, Folder 16)
    - Freeney, Ralph D., circa 1967 (Box 19, Folder 17)
    - Friedheim, David, 1985-1987 (Box 19, Folder 18)
    - Fryer, John, circa 1990s (Box 19, Folder 19)
    - Fujihara, Jun, 1966-1967 (Box 19, Folder 20)
    - Fuller, Emily, 1989 (Box 19, Folder 21)
    - Gablik, Suzi, 1970-1971 (Box 19, Folder 22)
    - Gabo, Naum, 1977 (Box 19, Folder 23)
    - Gabor, Attalai, 1966 (Box 19, Folder 24)
    - Galen, circa 1957-1981 (Box 19, Folder 25)
    - Galleries Magazine, 1995 (Box 19, Folder 26)
    - Galloway, Robert, 1980-1981; circa 1967 (Box 19, Folder 27)
    - Gambone, Bruno, 1962-1964 (Box 19, Folder 28)
    - Gardner, Char, 1991-1992 (Box 19, Folder 29)
    - Gaston, Bob, 1973 (Box 19, Folder 30)
    - Gatewood, Maud F., 1974-1976 (Box 19, Folder 31)
    - Geier, Dan, 1977 (Box 19, Folder 32)
    - Gelb, Jan, 1959 (Box 19, Folder 33)
    - General Services Administration (GSA), 1993-1994 (Box 19, Folder 34)
    - Geoffrey, J. Iqbal, 1963-1968 (Box 19, Folder 35-36)
    - George, Diane, 1975 (Box 19, Folder 37)
    - Gerard, Jonas, 1989-1995 (Box 19, Folder 38-39)
    - Gerstin, Marvin, 1989-1994 (Box 19, Folder 40)
    - Getz, Ilse, 1966; 1975 (Box 19, Folder 41)
    - Gibson, Ellen, 1994-1995 (Box 19, Folder 42)
    - Gillen, Ann, 1979-1985 (Box 20, Folder 1)
    - Gillespie, Dorothy, 1974 (Box 20, Folder 2)
    - Gillette, Dean, 1970-1975 (Box 20, Folder 3)
    - Gilliam, Sam, 1966 (Box 20, Folder 4)
    - Ginsberg, Elizabeth, 1973-1975 (Box 20, Folder 5)
    - Glading, Gay, 1968-1977 (Box 20, Folder 6)
    - Glidden, jjon, 1983-1993 (Box 20, Folder 7-10)
    - Glotzbach, Chris, 1984 (Box 20, Folder 11)
    - Going, Jo, 1973-1974 (Box 20, Folder 12)
    - Gold, Lloyd, circa 1978 (Box 20, Folder 13)
    - Goodman, Martin, Mrs., 1963-1976; 1987 (Box 20, Folder 14-15)
    - Goodyear, John, 1967-1972; 1987-1990 (Box 20, Folder 16-17)
    - Gorchov, Ron, 1974-1978 (Box 20, Folder 18)
    - Gordy, Robert, 1968 (Box 20, Folder 19)
    - Gorky, Arshile, 1963-1970 (Box 20, Folder 20)
    - Goryansky, Sergei, 1992-1995 (Box 20, Folder 21)
    - Gottlieb, Adolph, 1966-1972 (Box 20, Folder 22)
    - Gouverneur, Simon, 1984-1985 (Box 20, Folder 23)
    - Grabosky, Tom, 1988-1990 (Box 20, Folder 24)
    - Grabosky, Tom and Boston Artists, circa 1989 (Box 20, Folder 25)
    - Graham, Richard, 1978-1979 (Box 20, Folder 26)
    - Grant, Don, 1984-1992 (Box 20, Folder 27-29)
    - Grant, L.R., 1982 (Box 20, Folder 30)
    - Green, George, 1972-1976 (Box 20, Folder 31-32)
    - Greenberg, Alan, 1987 (Box 20, Folder 33)
    - Greenly, Colin, 1966-1974 (Box 20, Folder 34-36)
    - Greenwood, Kiisel, 1965-1970 (Box 21, Folder 1)
    - Greenwood, Tony, 1969-1973 (Box 21, Folder 2)
    - Griffin, Don, 1990-1995 (Box 21, Folder 3-4)
    - Griffin, Gerry, 1977-1980 (Box 21, Folder 5)
    - Griffin, Nicole, 1994-1995 (Box 21, Folder 6)
    - Griffin, Steve, 1979-1991 (Box 21, Folder 7-10)
    - Grika, Herb, 1965 (Box 21, Folder 11)
    - Grisanty, Aurelio, 1987; 1985 (Box 21, Folder 12)
    - Grooms, Red, 1973-1976 (Box 21, Folder 13)
    - Gross, Su, 1991 (Box 21, Folder 14)
    - Gross-Mario, Wolfgang, circa 1960s (Box 21, Folder 15)
    - Grote, Mark, 1986-1989 (Box 21, Folder 16)
    - Grow, Ronald, 1966-1977; 1985-1986 (Box 21, Folder 17-19)
      Oversized material housed in Box 56, Folder 5
    - Growden, Jim, 1976-1983 (Box 21, Folder 20)
    - Grusky, Lenne, 1978-1988 (Box 21, Folder 21)
    - Guberman, Sidney T., 1969-1978 (Box 21, Folder 22-23)
    - Gubernick, Richard, 1970-1992 (Box 21, Folder 24-26)
    - Guston, Philip, 1988 (Box 22, Folder 1)
    - Hackett, R.E., 1965 (Box 22, Folder 2)
    - Haddad, Farid, circa 1978 (Box 22, Folder 3)
    - Haerer, Carol, circa 1971 (Box 22, Folder 4)
    - Hagan, James, 1989-1991 (Box 22, Folder 5)
    - Hahn, William, circa 1987 (Box 22, Folder 6)
    - Halbrooks, Darryl, 1975 (Box 22, Folder 7)
    - Halegua, Alfredo, 1968-1977 (Box 22, Folder 8)
    - Hall, Blair and Michael, 1990-1995 (Box 22, Folder 9)
    - Hall, Joan, 1973 (Box 22, Folder 10)
    - Hall, Martha, 1971-1974 (Box 22, Folder 11)
    - Hall, Michael D., 1967-1968 (Box 22, Folder 12)
    - Hamburger, Sydney, 1978-1979 (Box 22, Folder 13)
    - Hamilton, Eugene Larry, 1973-1974 (Box 22, Folder 14)
    - Hammes, Manfred, 1987-1992 (Box 22, Folder 15-17)
    - Hammond, Harmony, 1979-1980 (Box 22, Folder 18)
    - Hampel, Harrison, circa 1957-1981 (Box 22, Folder 19)
    - Han, H.N., 1972-1978 (Box 22, Folder 20)
    - Hanna, Dan, 1975-1982 (Box 22, Folder 21)
    - Hansen, Randy, 1984-1993 (Box 22, Folder 22)
    - Hargrave, Robert, Plywood Sculpture, 1991 (Box 22, Folder 23)
    - Harholdt, Peter, 1972-1976 (Box 22, Folder 24-25)
    - Harms, Elizabeth, 1966 (Box 22, Folder 26)
    - Harrington, Dennis, 1985-1993 (Box 22, Folder 27-29)
    - Harris, Allen, 1964, undated (Box 22, Folder 30)
    - Harris, Paul, 1969-1978 (Box 22, Folder 31)
    - Hart, Gordon, 1964-1967 (Box 22, Folder 32)
    - Hartigan, Grace, 1959 (Box 22, Folder 33)
    - Hartley, Paul, 1995-1996 (Box 22, Folder 34)
    - Hattori, Hiroshi, circa 1968-1969 (Box 22, Folder 35)
    - Havard, James, 1970-1973 (Box 22, Folder 36)
    - Havenhand, Andrew, 1984-1987 (Box 22, Folder 37)
    - Hayes, David, 1989-1994; circa 1968 (Box 23, Folder 1)
    - Hayes, John, 1994 (Box 23, Folder 2)
    - Hayman, Chris, 1970-1978; 1986 (Box 23, Folder 3-5)
    - Heany, David, 1973-1974 (Box 23, Folder 6)
    - Hefferton, Philip, 1969-1990 (Box 23, Folder 7)
    - Heikoop, Govert, 1994-1996 (Box 23, Folder 8-9)
    - Heilmann, Mary, 1972-1976; 1989-1992 (Box 23, Folder 10-11)
    - Helander Gallery, 1990-1991 (Box 23, Folder 12)
    - Henderson, Gil, circa 1974 (Box 23, Folder 13)
    - Henderson, Jim, 1986-1991 (Box 23, Folder 14-15)
    - Henderson, Mary, 1977 (Box 23, Folder 16)
    - Hendricks, Ed, 1978-1981 (Box 23, Folder 17)
    - Hendricks, James, 1970 (Box 23, Folder 18)
    - Henri, 1953; circa 1980s; 1951 (Box 23, Folder 19)
    - Henry, Charles, 1969-1976 (Box 23, Folder 20)
    - Henry, Mary, circa 1970 (Box 23, Folder 21)
    - Henschel, David, 1977-1978 (Box 23, Folder 22)
    - Hepworth, Barbara, 1968; 1975 (Box 23, Folder 23)
    - Herbert, Mimi, 1969-1982; 1991 (Box 23, Folder 24-27)
    - Herbert, Mimi, 1971-circa 1981 (Box 24, Folder 1-3)
    - Herbert, Mimi, Photos for Critics, circa 1975-1980s (Box 24, Folder 4)
    - Heron, Patrick, 1971 (Box 24, Folder 5)
    - Herrmann, Frank, 1982-1994 (Box 24, Folder 6-9)
    - Heuser, Tayo, 1991-1995 (Box 24, Folder 10)
    - Hewit, Lisa, 1980-1981 (Box 24, Folder 11)
    - Higginbotham, Charles, 1994-1995 (Box 24, Folder 12)
    - Hilleary, James, 1974; 1968 (Box 24, Folder 13)
    - Hiltner, Franz-Peter, circa 1968-1971 (Box 24, Folder 14)
    - Hinkle, Debra, 1993 (Box 24, Folder 15)
    - Hinkley, Marc, circa 1985-1986 (Box 24, Folder 16)
    - Hintz, Sally, 1974 (Box 24, Folder 17)
    - Hirshhorn Museum and Sculpture Garden, Information, 1977-1988 (Box 24, Folder 18)
    - Hoagg, Douglas, 1986-1994 (Box 24, Folder 19-22)
    - Hodges, 1973 (Box 24, Folder 23)
    - Hoeydonck, 1966 (Box 24, Folder 24)
    - Hoffmann, Hans, 1978; 1960 (Box 24, Folder 25)
    - Hofmann, George, 1984-1987 (Box 24, Folder 26)
    - Holcomb, Tom, 1970-1980 (Box 24, Folder 27)
    - Holland, Susan Lynn, circa 1970 (Box 24, Folder 28)
    - Holland, Tom, 1969-1973 (Box 24, Folder 29)
    - Holocaust Memorial Museum, 1993 (Box 24, Folder 30)
    - Hom, Jem, 1963 (Box 24, Folder 31)
    - Hompson, Davi Det, 1991-1995; circa 1969 (Box 24, Folder 32)
    - Hompson, Davi Det [and Leslie Exton and Anthony Cafritz], circa 1994 (Box 24, Folder 33)
    - Hoots, Milo, 1985 (Box 24, Folder 34)
    - Hopkins, Budd, 1966; before 1982 (Box 24, Folder 35)
    - Hopps, Walter, 1991 (Box 24, Folder 36)
    - Horn, Steve, 1971-1980 (Box 24, Folder 37)
    - Horton, Sheldon, 1992-1995 (Box 24, Folder 38)
    - Howdershell, William, circa 1970s-1996 (Box 24, Folder 39)
    - Huberman, Jeffrey, 1990 (Box 25, Folder 1)
    - Huebler, Douglas, circa 1959-1966 (Box 25, Folder 2)
    - Hughes, Robert (art critic), 1983-1993 (Box 25, Folder 3)
    - Hundertwasser, Friedrich, 1968 (Box 25, Folder 4)
    - Hunt, Richard, 1975 (Box 25, Folder 5)
    - Hunter, Robert, 1965 (Box 25, Folder 6)
    - Huntington Block, 1991-1993 (Box 25, Folder 7-8)
    - Hyland, Sharka Brod, 1984-1986 (Box 25, Folder 9)
    - Hynes, Hillary, 1967-1970 (Box 25, Folder 10)
    - Ichihashi, Taro, 1973-1995 (Box 25, Folder 11-15)
    - Ikinaga, George, 1980-1987 (Box 25, Folder 16-17)
    - Indiana, Robert, 1965-1973 (Box 25, Folder 18)
    - Ingram, O'Neal, 1971-1978 (Box 25, Folder 19)
    - International Sculpture Center, 1990 (Box 25, Folder 20)
    - Irwin, Robert, circa 1970s (Box 25, Folder 21)
    - Ishida, Traute, 1971-1990 (Box 25, Folder 22-26)
    - Ishida, Traute, 1974-1990 (Box 26, Folder 1-3)
    - Jackson, A.B., 1986 (Box 26, Folder 4)
    - Jackson, Bill, 1994 (Box 26, Folder 5)
      Oversized material housed in Box 56, Folder 6
    - Jackson, Herrick, 1983-1984 (Box 26, Folder 6)
    - Jackson, William, 1992; 1994 (Box 26, Folder 7)
    - Jacobshagen, Susanne, 1978 (Box 26, Folder 8)
    - Javacheff, Christo, 1970s (Box 26, Folder 9)
    - Jefferies, Mackey, 1971 (Box 26, Folder 10)
    - Jensen, Bob, circa 1979-1990s (Box 26, Folder 11-13)
    - Jewesson, Kenneth, circa 1974-1988 (Box 26, Folder 14)
    - Jimenez, Luis A., 1969-1970 (Box 26, Folder 15)
    - Johnson, Jerome, circa 1970-1971 (Box 26, Folder 16-18)
    - Johnson, Ray, 1966 (Box 26, Folder 19)
    - Jones, Gregory A., 1973-1976 (Box 26, Folder 20)
    - Jones, James R., 1976 (Box 26, Folder 21)
    - Jones, Patrick, 1974-1986 (Box 26, Folder 22-25)
    - Jones, William, 1969-1989 (Box 26, Folder 26-27)
    - Jones, William, 1969; 1977-1989 (Box 27, Folder 1)
    - Joseph, Eric, 1979-1995 (Box 27, Folder 2-4)
    - Josephson, Janna Waldinger, 1982-1983 (Box 27, Folder 5)
    - Jubran, Hanna, 1995 (Box 27, Folder 6)
    - Judson, Jeannette, 1973-1974 (Box 27, Folder 7)
    - Kagan, Larry, circa 1976; 1993-1994 (Box 27, Folder 8)
    - Kangas, Gene, 1970 (Box 27, Folder 9)
    - Kanol, Karl, circa late 1950s (Box 27, Folder 10)
    - Kaplan, Jacques, 1975 (Box 27, Folder 11)
    - Kaprelia, Charles E., circa 1967 (Box 27, Folder 12)
    - Karis, Peter, 1995; 1992 (Box 27, Folder 13)
    - Katz, Margie Billstein, 1978-1980 (Box 27, Folder 14)
    - Katzen, Lila, 1965, circa 1970 (Box 27, Folder 15)
    - Kaufman, Gail Hope, 1973 (Box 27, Folder 16)
    - Kaufman, Jane, 1988-1995; circa 1973-1974 (Box 27, Folder 17)
    - Kawakami, Takanori, circa 1966-1968 (Box 27, Folder 18)
    - Kawakawa, 1968 (Box 27, Folder 19)
    - Kayse, Gene, 1971 (Box 27, Folder 20)
    - Kazanskaya, Katya, 1994-1995 (Box 27, Folder 21)
    - Keck, Jeanne, 1994 (Box 27, Folder 22)
    - Keinholz, Ed, 1966 (Box 27, Folder 23)
    - Kelley, Ed, 1967 (Box 27, Folder 24)
    - Kelly, Ellsworth, 1968-1975; 1992 (Box 27, Folder 25)
    - Kemper Insurance Co., 1973-1980 (Box 27, Folder 26)
    - Kendall, Tom, 1984; 1964-1967 (Box 27, Folder 27-29)
    - Kessler, Alan, circa 1991; 1973-1974 (Box 27, Folder 30)
    - Kidner, Michael and Larry Kagan, 1970s (Box 27, Folder 31)
    - King, Gerald, 1970 (Box 27, Folder 32)
    - King, Kevin, 1992-1995 (Box 27, Folder 33)
    - Kinnee, Sandy, 1977-1978 (Box 27, Folder 34)
    - Kirk, Jerome, 1967-1990 (Box 27, Folder 35-37)
    - Kisch, Gloria, 1973 (Box 27, Folder 38)
    - Kitayama, Yoshio, 1983-1990 (Box 28, Folder 1-3)
    - Kline, Richard, 1967-1974 (Box 28, Folder 4-5)
    - Kliros, Theodore, 1965-1966 (Box 28, Folder 6)
    - Knight, Bunyon Nathaniel, 1977-1980 (Box 28, Folder 7)
    - Knight, Nathaniel, circa 1971 (Box 28, Folder 8)
    - Knowlton, Grace, 1970-1995 (Box 28, Folder 9-12)
    - Kogelnik, Kiki, 1964-1994 (Box 28, Folder 13-21)
    - Kohlberg, Bety, 1977-1978 (Box 29, Folder 1)
    - Kohler, Lucartha, 1981 (Box 29, Folder 2)
    - Kohlmeyer, Ida, 1962-1989 (Box 29, Folder 3-7)
    - Kohlmeyer, Ida, Photographs of Artwork, undated (Box 29, Folder 8)
    - Kolibal, Stanislav, 1979-1987 (Box 29, Folder 9-10)
    - Kollwitz, Kathe, 1992 (Box 29, Folder 11)
    - Kornbluth, Frances, 1991-1995 (Box 29, Folder 12-14)
    - Korpi, Neil Hartley, circa 1971 (Box 29, Folder 15)
    - Kortlander, John, 1984-1985 (Box 29, Folder 16)
    - Kostka, Dale, 1966-1975 (Box 29, Folder 17)
    - Kraft, James, 1978 (Box 29, Folder 18)
    - Kreykenbohm, William, 1975-1981 (Box 29, Folder 19)
    - Kristoffy, Joyce Ann, 1970; 1988-1989 (Box 29, Folder 20)
    - Kristofori, Jan, 1974; 1981-1986 (Box 29, Folder 21)
    - Krulich, Sara and Andy, 1992 (Box 29, Folder 22)
    - Krushenick, Nicholas, 1965 (Box 29, Folder 23)
    - Kulak, Gary, 1982-1990 (Box 29, Folder 24-26)
    - Kurhajec, Joseph, 1971-1973 (Box 29, Folder 27)
    - Kuter, Leslie, 1974-1975 (Box 29, Folder 28)
    - Kuwayama, Tadaaki, 1966-1978 (Box 29, Folder 29)
    - Kyrakos, Aleko, 1967 (Box 29, Folder 30)
    - La Noue, Terence David, 1973-1977 (Box 29, Folder 31)
    - Lable, Elliot, 1978 (Box 30, Folder 1)
    - Lamm, Leonid, 1985 (Box 30, Folder 2)
    - Lang, Daniel, circa 1968-1969 (Box 30, Folder 3)
    - Langston, William H., circa 1970 (Box 30, Folder 4)
    - Lasch, Patricia, circa 1973 (Box 30, Folder 5)
      Oversized material housed in Box 56, Folder 7
    - Lassaw, Ibram, 1975-1977; 1961 (Box 30, Folder 6)
    - Lassman, Vivienne H., 1990 (Box 30, Folder 7)
    - Latham, John, circa 1957-1981 (Box 30, Folder 8)
    - Lathrop, June, 1983-1991; 1964 (Box 30, Folder 9-10)
    - Lavatelli, Carla, 1974 (Box 30, Folder 11)
    - Leaf, Joe, 1973 (Box 30, Folder 12)
    - Leavitt, Ruth, 1974-1975 (Box 30, Folder 13)
    - Lehman, Joan, circa 1957-1981 (Box 30, Folder 14)
    - Leipziger, Mary, 1975-1981 (Box 30, Folder 15)
    - Leland, Whitney E., 1971 (Box 30, Folder 16)
    - Leon, Dennis, 1981; 1964-1965 (Box 30, Folder 17)
    - Lerner, Leslie, 1978-1993 (Box 30, Folder 18-19)
    - Leventhal, Katya, 1991-1995 (Box 30, Folder 20)
    - Levine, Les, 1986-1987; 1971; 1969 (Box 30, Folder 21-22)
    - Levy, Ellen K., 1979-1985 (Box 30, Folder 23)
    - Levy, Estelle, 1990-1994 (Box 30, Folder 24)
    - LeWitt, Sol, circa 1970s-1981 (Box 30, Folder 25)
    - Lichtenstein, Roy, 1993-1995 (Box 30, Folder 26)
    - Lichtman, Stuart, 1991; 1983-1985 (Box 30, Folder 27)
    - Lick, Dennis, 1981-1989 (Box 30, Folder 28-29)
    - Lindenmann, Robert, circa 1976-1977 (Box 30, Folder 30)
    - Lipman, Howard, 1971 (Box 30, Folder 31)
    - Lister, Ardele, 1977 (Box 30, Folder 32)
    - Lloyd, Elliott, circa 1973 (Box 30, Folder 33)
    - Loeb, Judy, circa 1970-1971 (Box 30, Folder 34)
    - Lollar, Tom, 1981 (Box 30, Folder 35)
    - Londin, Barbara, 1993-1995 (Box 30, Folder 36)
    - Loomis, Michael, 1985-1990 (Box 30, Folder 37-38)
    - Louis, Morris, 1962-1973 (Box 30, Folder 39)
    - Loveless, Jim, circa 1970s-1981 (Box 30, Folder 40)
    - Luber, Mal, 1972, undated (Box 30, Folder 41)
    - Lucas, William, 1974-1982 (Box 30, Folder 42)
    - Luttrell, Brewster?, circa 1985 (Box 30, Folder 43)
    - Lutz, Ed, 1965 (Box 30, Folder 44)
    - Lutz, Robert, circa 1965 (Box 30, Folder 45)
    - Lyke, Tyler, 1992-1995 (Box 31, Folder 1)
    - Lyndon, Alice, circa 1977 (Box 31, Folder 2)
    - Machine Tools, 1969-1970; 1980 (Box 31, Folder 3)
      Oversized material housed in Box 56, Folder 8
    - Madlener, Richard, 1967 (Box 31, Folder 4)
    - Mahaffey, Noel, 1970-1971 (Box 31, Folder 5)
    - Maisel, Georg, circa 1960s-1981 (Box 31, Folder 6)
    - Malevich, Kazimir, 1990-1991 (Box 31, Folder 7)
    - Malina, Frank, 1968 (Box 31, Folder 8)
    - Malino, Emily, 1974 (Box 31, Folder 9)
    - Mallinson, Constance, 1984; 1973-1976 (Box 31, Folder 10)
    - Mangold, Robert, 1965 (Box 31, Folder 11)
    - Manno, John, circa 1963-1969 (Box 31, Folder 12)
    - Mapplethorpe, Robert, 1989-1990 (Box 31, Folder 13)
    - Maps, Edward Howard, 1963 (Box 31, Folder 14)
    - Marcus, Marcia, circa 1969 (Box 31, Folder 15)
    - Markowski, 1967 (Box 31, Folder 16)
    - Maroger, Jacques, 1960 (Box 31, Folder 17)
    - Marsh, Reginald, 1967 (Box 31, Folder 18)
    - Marshall, John, 1988-1989 (Box 31, Folder 19)
    - Martin, David, 1989-1995 (Box 31, Folder 20-22)
    - Martin, Fran, 1979 (Box 31, Folder 23)
    - Matusz, John, 1990 (Box 31, Folder 24)
    - Maul, John, 1978-1980 (Box 31, Folder 25)
    - Maza, Fernando, 1963 (Box 31, Folder 26)
    - Mazoh, Stephen, 1992; 1977 (Box 31, Folder 27)
    - McCarthy, Hamilton, circa 1957-1981 (Box 31, Folder 28)
    - McChesney, Clifton, 1968 (Box 31, Folder 29)
    - McCoy, Jason, 1977-1978 (Box 31, Folder 30)
    - McCullough, David, circa 1971-1973 (Box 31, Folder 31)
    - McCurdy, Maggie, circa 1970s (Box 31, Folder 32-33)
    - McDonald, Barbara, 1971-1972 (Box 31, Folder 34)
    - McEntyre, Eduardo, 1967 (Box 31, Folder 35)
    - McFarland, James, 1994 (Box 31, Folder 36)
    - McGowin, Ed, 1964-1980 (Box 31, Folder 37)
    - McGowin, Ed (1962) (Box 31, Folder 38)
    - McGowin, Ed (1963), 1969; 1963-1964 (Box 31, Folder 39)
    - McGowin, Ed (1964) (Box 32, Folder 1)
    - McGowin, Ed (1965) (Box 32, Folder 2)
    - McGowin, Ed (1966), 1966-1967 (Box 32, Folder 3)
    - McGowin, Ed (1967) (Box 32, Folder 4)
    - McGowin, Ed (1968) (Box 32, Folder 5)
    - McGowin, Ed (1969) (Box 32, Folder 6-7)
    - McGowin, Ed (1970) (Box 32, Folder 8)
    - McGowin, Ed (1971) (Box 32, Folder 9)
    - McGowin, Ed (1972) (Box 32, Folder 10)
    - McGowin, Ed (1974) (Box 32, Folder 11)
    - McGowin, Ed (1977, 1980) (Box 32, Folder 12)
    - McGowin, Ed (Undated), circa 1962-1980 (Box 32, Folder 13)
    - McGowin, Ed, Duplicate Material, 1968-1970 (Box 32, Folder 14)
    - McGowin, Ed, "True Stories" (Corcoran Gallery of Art), 1975 (Box 32, Folder 15)
    - McIvor, John W., 1963-1964 (Box 32, Folder 16)
    - McLaughlin, John, 1967-1975 (Box 32, Folder 17)
    - McLaughlin, John, Nebraska, 1993; 1969-1971 (Box 32, Folder 18)
    - McLean, James, 1974 (Box 32, Folder 19)
    - McMullin, M.A., 1995 (Box 32, Folder 20)
    - McRae, Ralph, 1971; 1977 (Box 32, Folder 21)
    - Meadmore, Clement, 1975 (Box 32, Folder 22)
    - Mefferd, Boyd, 1970-1971 (Box 32, Folder 23)
    - Mehring, Howard, 1962-1970 (Box 32, Folder 24)
    - Mendizabal, Victor, circa early 1960s (Box 32, Folder 25)
    - Menil, de, circa 1986 (Box 32, Folder 26)
    - Merkin, Richard, 1967 (Box 32, Folder 27)
    - Merline, Mark, 1991-1995 (Box 32, Folder 28)
    - Miami-Dade Community College, 1972-1976 (Box 32, Folder 29)
    - Middlebrook, David, circa 1971 (Box 32, Folder 30)
    - Miller, George, 1967-1971 (Box 32, Folder 31-33)
    - Miller, Jane, 1961 (Box 32, Folder 34)
    - Mims, Jack, 1971-1972 (Box 32, Folder 35)
    - Minnesota State Arts Board, Information, 1984 (Box 32, Folder 36)
    - Miretsky, Anya, 1994-1995 (Box 32, Folder 37)
    - Miretsky, David, 1994 (Box 32, Folder 38)
    - Miró, Joan, 1993 (Box 32, Folder 39)
    - Mishima, Kimiyo, 1974-1988 (Box 33, Folder 1-2)
    - Mitchell, Gerald E., 1985-1988 (Box 33, Folder 3)
    - Mitchell, James, circa 1986 (Box 33, Folder 4)
    - Mittendorf, George, undated (Box 33, Folder 5)
    - Mladek, Meda, 1960s-1980 (Box 33, Folder 6)
    - Modigliani, Amadeo, 1965 (Box 33, Folder 7)
    - Mogavero, Michael, 1976-1977 (Box 33, Folder 8)
    - Moholy-Nagy, László, 1975 (Box 33, Folder 9)
    - Molna'l?, Peter, 1987 (Box 33, Folder 10)
    - Mondino, Aldo, 1964 (Box 33, Folder 11)
    - Mones, David, 1973-1974 (Box 33, Folder 12)
    - Montgomery, Kathleen, 1985-1987 (Box 33, Folder 13)
    - Montgomery, Nan, 1977 (Box 33, Folder 14)
    - Moore, Henry, 1972-1973 (Box 33, Folder 15)
    - Moore, Lansing, 1982-1995 (Box 33, Folder 16)
    - Moore, William, 1994-1995 (Box 33, Folder 17)
    - Moquin, Richard, circa 1986 (Box 33, Folder 18)
    - Morais, 1967 (Box 33, Folder 19)
    - Morandi, Georgio, circa 1980s-1996 (Box 33, Folder 20)
    - Moreland, Dave, 1981-1995 (Box 33, Folder 21-25)
    - Morell, Gregory, 1983 (Box 33, Folder 26)
    - Morgan, John D., circa 1976 (Box 33, Folder 27)